(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T23:47:57.581500",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I miss her.
I miss her so much!
When was the last time we saw her?
She hasn't left her room in two weeks.
Does this mean... she doesn't love us anymore?!
Fear not, my friends.
Is that Jailboss?
Jailboss?
JAILBOSS?!
Tonight, we infiltrate her bedroom.
Follow me, I know a secret passage. Shh!
Wait, no!
Retreat!
How dare you enter my room!
Don't mess with a girl's sleepover!
生まれた
Born into the world...
赤い花
...a red flower,
只、孤独に
just swaying...
ゆらゆら 解答の無いまま
...in solitude, without an answer.
生まれた
Born,
赤い花
a red flower.
只、孤独に ゆらゆら
Just swaying in solitude.
解答の無い 儀
Without a single answer given,
弁明は脆く愚かな結末
excuses lead to a fragile, foolish end.
貼り付けにされた 心は泣いてる
A heart nailed to a cross is weeping.
両手から落ちる この雫が
These teardrops falling from both hands,
貴方には見えていないのでしょう
surely you cannot see them, can you?
なら 此処まで
Then come this far.
悲しい声に コトバに 追い遣られて
Driven away by sorrowful voices, by words...
俯いたまま 微笑む 赤い花
...a red flower smiling with bowed head.
深く根を張る 痛みが 贖罪なら
If the deeply rooted pain is penance...
解り合えない
...we will never understand each other.
ずっとこのまま
Remaining just like this forever.
変わらない定め
Unchanging destiny...
真理は不条理
...truth is absurd.
剥き出しされた 感覚の違い
Differences in naked senses...
ありふれた“言葉”を 振りかざす
...wielding commonplace "words".
貴方には見えていないのでしょう
Surely you cannot see them, can you?
もう 消えない 傷
A wound that will never heal.
風の吹く夜に
On a night when the wind blows...
散ってしまう花の色を
...the color of the flowers scattering away...
貴方は知ることもきっと ないのでしょう
...surely you will never even know.
底の底まで 堕ちたら
When you fall to the very bottom...
黒い景色
...a pitch-black scenery.
俯いたまま 泣いてた 赤い花
A red flower weeping with bowed head.
朽ちていく心の中まだ願ってる
Inside a decaying heart, I am still wishing...
ありのまま生きていたいと
...to live just as I am.
悲しい声に コトバに 追い遣られて
Driven away by sorrowful voices, by words...
俯いたまま 散り行く アネモネ
...an anemone scattering with bowed head.
深く根を張る 痛みが 消えなくても
Even if the deeply rooted pain does not vanish...
足掻き続ける
...I will keep struggling.
何度だって
No matter how many times...
淡い想いに
...toward faint feelings...
手を伸ばして
...reaching out my hands.
Little darling!
My love, where are you?
Hello? Are you over here? Ah!
Oh, there you are!
My darling!
Oh, you look so cute laying on my bed like that!
Isn't he just adorable?
I just want to squeeze him, but I'll leave him be for the time being.
Jailbirds, I have to welcome you...
...to my room, as this is a very, very special day.
Do you know? Do you remember?
That today is my... birthday!
In case you don't know me, let me quick introduce myself.
In case you don't know me, let me quickly introduce myself.
Hiya darlings! This is Hololive English Advent's devilish diva...
...the one, the only, Nerissa Ravencroft...
...and I'm so happy to have you in here for my room debut!
Being able to celebrate with you guys is so amazing,
but I thought it would be more fun if I had some friends with me.
So, I've invited some very special people today.
Would you guys please come on in?
Yay! Welcome!
We're home! We're home!
Happy birthday!
Party time!
Hello! We're here today!
...to celebrate Nerissa's birthday!
Thank you all for coming!
No, you're here for me, right?
No, they're here for me!
We're here to look at your bed.
Uh, yes! What do you guys think, by the way?
It's so cute! I'm glad!
I want to show off some details...
...because I know you guys have been here before,
but this is the Jailbirds' first ever time seeing my room!
So let me go ahead and point out some of the details.
First, because everyone is so interested in it,
I want to highlight the bed area.
In this area, we have a lot of my personal plushies...
...and my cat! He does have another cat bed, but he likes to sleep there.
It's also, it's very princessy, right? Just like me, right?
Babygirl coded!
I also have a beautiful painting right above my bed.
And I see something else there... Is that a Jailbird?
No, no way, that's not a Jailbird, right?
Who knows?
Then, behind me, over behind Fuwamoco...
...there is this beautiful vanity area.
It makes me feel even more princessy.
You can see there is a bust of my head.
Wow, you have a bust made of yourself?
It's important! It's important.
I also have Renaissance paintings...
...scattered throughout the room, too.
You might notice them, I have little Advent references.
There's a Pero hiding, some are over here.
Oh, so cute!
Up there, I have a Novalite.
And then over here, over by the vanity area, there's a little Jio.
So, lots of little Advent references...
...all around for you to enjoy.
So, yeah, that's awesome, right?
That's it!
Alright, time to leave! Wait, what?
Thank you for having us!
We're leaving now! Bye!
You're leaving? What? You're not leaving!
We saw your cat, so we're good!
Are you gonna have us do anything while we're here?
Yes! Well, I've prepared...
...a very special game today, actually.
I think you guys are gonna have a lot of fun!
It's something a little out of the ordinary.
So, today, you must treat me like your princesses.
Well, like your princess, actually.
No, I'm your princess...
...and you are my princes.
So, it's going to be a blind date!
You have to make my heart flutter a lot,
and make me feel amazing on my birthday.
I guess that sounds like fun then!
I'm the one being rizzed in this game.
I'm excited to see your unexpected sides!
So, I need to prep everything in my room,
so I need you all to get over there.
No, no, just over there.
In the corner?
I'm gonna set up everything, okay?
I'm gonna set up.
Wait, what's going on? We're spinning!
Are we supposed to get dizzy like this?
I'm gonna pull everything, okay?
Just don't worry, the...
...furniture is a little heavy.
Spin her around!
I have everything almost ready!
Okay, okay...
Okay, what do you guys think?
A chair? It exists!
The color doesn't match the room's theme though, no?
It's fine, I'm going to be sitting
in this chair right here,
and I'm going to put on a blindfold, too.
Oh! What? Why? Why?
Don't worry, don't worry. Piyanas,
on this projector...
Piyanas! Piyanas! Piyanas!
You guys can relax, okay? Relax.
And come close to me. You're so far away.
Okay...
So, on this projector here, there's going to be prompts
with various questions, and situations will appear,
so you all have to answer them one by one.
Your voices are going to be altered with the voice changer.
So... Is it going to be cute?
Yeah, but I'm not going to be able to know who's talking.
Oh.
So, based on that, I won't have any preconceptions
about anyone because it'll just be based on your rizz alone.
So feel free to be extra romantic, okay?
What's wrong with you? Don't worry about it.
We'll do our best to be romantic then, high-five!
Yeah! Let's start!
[Cellmate's in Love] The name of the game is Cellmate's in Love!
Yay!
The questions for everyone will be displayed on the projector screen,
so please read them carefully.
But I must put my blindfold on now.
Oh!
Okay, so I guess she won't know who's answering,
so the person should move quietly, so she doesn't know the order.
Yeah.
And plus we have a voice changer.
Right.
Okay, well, we should probably line up now, huh?
Ah, okay.
Who wants to go first? I don't know.
How about... I think you should go first.
Okay, we can do answering in this order then.
Yeah!
Okay.
Now, give us the first question!
[Cellmate's in Love / First Date] First Date!
First Date!
It's been over two years since Rissa and I became friends...
But I think it's time to take our relationship beyond friendship!
But, I'm scared I might ruin what we have...
Oh!
But... I really want to tell her how I feel!
So, gather your courage, and finally decide to ask Rissa out on a date!
What would you say to ask her out,
and where would you like to go for your first date?
Try to ask her smoothly!
That was a lot.
Okay, so it's all just a hypothetical situation, right?
Right. So on-point, isn't it?
We all have to figure out how to ask her out.
You know, considering how we are now, right?
Right.
Well, you are ready then.
Okay.
Bye!
[How Nerissa hears it / Nerissaにはこう聞こえています]
Nerissa.
You know,
I've been thinking.
You're really important to me,
and I'd like to go out somewhere special together.
And, I...
maybe we have some time,
just the two of us.
You know?
So...
I was thinking,
maybe...
we could go to that cafe that you said you liked a few months ago?
Oh, your favorite, right?
Oh, we could go there,
have a nice evening, and then maybe...
you know, once our tummies are all full,
then, we can go on a bit of a stroll,
enjoy, you know, the city lights,
maybe the water,
uh...
Would you like that?
I would like that! That sounds so sweet!
Well, then...
it's a date.
Okay.
Let's do it.
So romantic.
Okay, I did my best.
You did great!
Good job, good job. I'll go next.
Do your best! Yeah!
Show her what you're made of.
Okay, clear your throat, make it a little bit flat for me.
I don't think you need that.
She'll tell though. You're loud.
You're cool. Right, right.
This is kind of mean, isn't it?
Well, whatever.
Deal with it! Try, try!
Okay, I'm ready, I'm ready.
Hey, Nerissa.
You and me, movies tonight.
Come or don't.
But if you don't, you're going to miss...
you're going to miss out on so much, baby.
You know what we're going to do at the movies?
We're going to pick the scariest movie ever.
And then...
I...
...am going to be such a beeping wimp.
I'm gonna cry.
I'm gonna...
cringe at the jump scares.
I'm gonna be so beeping scared, you're gonna have to comfort me.
And then you're gonna have to put your arm around my shoulder...
...and be like, "It's okay, sweetie."
You'll be fine.
And then I'm gonna... I'm gonna nuzzle myself into your chest.
Yeah...
...while you comfort me.
And we're gonna bond over fear.
And it's gonna be the most amazing thing ever.
Please... Oh my gosh, that sounds...
...come to the movies with me! Or not, it doesn't matter!
That also sounds so enthralling.
Woah, I'm kind of interested.
Sounds like a booty call.
But I'm a little scared, too.
I feel like I'm gonna have to be the one comforting you. I don't know how I feel about that.
That's the point.
Yeah, that's the point.
Well, that's a good... okay, let's move on to the next person then, how about?
Good job.
Nice try! Next person.
Who's next?
After that, you have to show off.
Get going.
I'm waiting!
That was actually pretty good. Impressive.
Rissa-chan...
...well...
...you know...
...we've been close for a little while now.
As compared to friends, right?
But...
...we've never really been able to hang out just the two of us, you know?
So...
...I think I'd really like it if it was just you and myself.
That's what I was thinking.
And maybe we could go...
...and get a massage together.
And then...
...afterwards...
...once we feel so much more relaxed...
...and free...
...we could go to a cafe!
A cafe that's very special to me.
Because I know you're a little indecisive, too.
And then, we could just chat...
...and... more.
More? Oh...
That sounds so fun, too.
You guys are really speaking to my, to my heart here with these cafes...
...and dates and stuff.
I like it a lot. I think we have one more contestant.
So, bachelor number four, will you please take the stage?
Ganbare! Go, Shiori!
Make it romantic!
I would go on a date with you.
No thank you.
My lady.
Pulls out 10 million dollars in cash...
...waves it under your nose.
This is all for you. And you know what? Not only that...
...but I have 10 million roses in the ground.
They all don't die, just like my love for you.
That's how it's supposed to be.
You are as beautiful as the moon, so bright, so elegant...
...so in the night sky.
I love seeing you at night, man.
Sorry, what are we doing for this date?
I was like, I forgot about the date.
Go on a date with me!
Okay, you've convinced me. I think all of you have successfully managed...
...to rizz me on a date.
So there's our first question.
Yay!
Let me get my cash again. She dropped her cash.
I can't tell who my favorite is yet. I think we're going to need some more questions...
...for me to be able to pick.
What? There's more? Yay!
Alright, well, let's move on to the next question then.
All right. We successfully ask Nerissa out, and she happily said yes!
Since it's our first date, we want to make her feel special and happy, right?
Right!
Well, what kind of surprise do we have in store for our first date?
A surprise! Yes, I love surprises!
I'm looking forward to it.
Now, the question is, are we going to continue the story of our first date?
Yeah! Let's do that!
Okay, blindfold back on.
Okay.
All right, I'm ready to be rizzed.
All right, well...
And we're ready to rizz you.
Let's go in order of rizz then.
Okay, that means...
...here I go!
She's so brave.
So then...
...during our date...
...while we're walking along the water at night with all the city lights around us...
...suddenly, you lose sight of me.
Huh?
Where could she be, though?
You feel a bit panicked, and then suddenly...
...you see a bunch of mascot characters.
Oh?
And they're doing a little bit of a dance. Uh, uh, ah, uh...
And then, all of a sudden, one of them goes...
"Wha!" And out comes... me!
A bit of a surprise!
And... I have roses.
And I say, "You're the character of my life."
"For you."
So cute!
That's so romantic, Bachelor Number One!
Thank you!
Romance, yeah!
Okay!
Good. / Thank you!
Yeah!
Romance!
All right, next up...
Let's go, my little Rizz Champion.
Still the mic is... Okay, well, whatever.
All right, Nerissa. After our date, you know...
...you have to take me home because...
...I spilled my drink all over myself from being scared because you were comforting me, right?
And so, afterwards, I take you home...
...to my place.
And you know what we're going to do? We open the door...
...and there's trash everywhere!
And that is my surprise, because I know everything about you, and I know that you love cleaning.
So, surprise! My room is dirty and you have to clean it.
And you love that so much, and that is so romantic for you. I'm like...
"Yeah, woman, clean my house."
And... I let you. I let you clean my house...
...and you feel so strong.
You know, I do love to clean.
Yeah.
Especially for my friends. However, I think if I was on a romantic date...
...it would not be at the top of my list. / But in the trash, there is treasures for you...
...that I put in the trash, like flowers. There's like, flowers...
...you'll have to dig for.
I think I would be... I think I would be turned off by that.
I feel like when I found them, I might be like, "Oh, that's cute," but I might be a little...
You did your best, so let's move on to the next one, how about that?
No one understands me.
This is my romance!
Okay, who's next?
Did you like it? Good job.
I'll do my best.
Wow...
You know, here at this cafe...
...I guess you're really excited for the cakes that we ordered, right?
And, well...
...I wanted to surprise you.
And I know there's one thing that you love very much.
So...
Nerissa...
...look me in the eyes.
You see this here?
This is my smartphone.
（バタン）机を叩く！
(Slam) Slam on the table!
Oh!
Today, I'm giving you all my attention...
...because you're my princess.
And today, it's just you and me.
Whoa! The rest of the world disappears when we're together for you? That's such a good surprise!
I love it so far, Bachelor Number Three!
All right, let's hear the last Bachelor, shall we?
That was a good one. / Yeah.
Good job. / Yeah, I'm sad. I'm sad.
My lady...
...as we walk on the moon where our date takes place in...
...I reconstructed...
...it from the ground up.
There is an amusement park in your honor, in your name...
...Nerissa Rivenland!
And there are jailbirds as far as the eye can see.
And you, each one serves you to the utmost ability they have. You can even step on them. That is my surprise.
An entire army just for you, a fat flock.
Oh my gosh, that is kind of romantic. / Yeah!
But I think they do that for me regardless. I don't think I need someone to set that up.
But they're moon jailbirds.
They're moon jailbirds?
They're moon jailbirds. It's like a whole different species.
Are they like white-colored, too, then?
Yes, they're also maybe fatter.
Ah! / Fed on my love for you.
What?
You feed them with your love?
That's how they survive.
Well, thank you, Bachelor Number Four.
No problem.
That was awesome. These are all awesome dates.
Well, even mine?
Ooh.
Well, it was a good attempt.
Everyone did so well!
Let's move on to the next question, shall we?
All right!
Question number three! The surprise was a huge success...
Ah, but even on this special date,
you'll feel frustrated that your "just friends" vibe
has not gone away yet.
Um, now, you want Nerissa to see you as more than a friend,
and you want her... you want her to think of you as like, a... more of like, a romantic interest?
So, it's time to make your move!
How are you going to do it? Say something to win her heart!
Please do win my heart, Advent!
Don't look.
Is that possible?
Yeah, it's... I'll put my blindfold back on, and you guys can come up with...
...everything you want to say.
Need to think.
Um...
Well, thinking time is over. Bachelor number one, would you please approach the mic?
Say something. Say something. Say something to make her more than friends.
Oh, I see, I see.
Things look, uh, uh, yeah.
Go, go Bill! Let's go!
Yeah, um, I'm Bill.
Bill?
Nerissa...
You know, we spent a lot of time together.
Um, I think I know you pretty well.
I would hope that you would think the same of me, but...
I feel like, you know,
I'd like to take things a step further.
You know, we're not just friends anymore, right?
So...
Can I...
Can I hold your hand?
Please, princess?
You can, you can hold my hand,
if you want to.
I'll... I'll hold your hand.
That's enough!
Thank you! That's so sweet!
Hand-holding? That's such a big advancement of our relationship.
But I'd still like to hear Bachelor number two.
Good luck. I got this. You got this.
Trash.
You tried to say "trash"? Go, William!
I'm William.
All right, baby. I'm gonna run over here.
Wh-what? No, wait!
You hear me in your ear, right? Yeah.
Smell me right now.
You smell like trash!
I smell good, I smell good, see? That's the pheromones, baby.
That means you're attracted.
If you think I smell good too, that means you like me so much.
You're so attracted to me, so I say we should take our relationship to the next level.
What do you say?
You're too close! Is that a yes?
Maybe.
I enjoyed that aggressiveness a little bit, I think.
Yeah, you gotta squeeze her hand gently.
Yeah, but it's...
Maybe just a little forceful. Maybe just a little sudden.
Cuz in your dirty, in your dirty room with all your dirty trash
and your dirty flowers underneath the trash...
When it's just you and me, baby, in the moment, you will forget about everything.
I see. Well, let's move on to Bachelor number three.
You can do this. You can do it. What's her name?
Go, Matilda! Matilda!
Matilda? Why was I Bill?
Why not?
Nerissa...
We had some very nice times together.
Just you and me.
And, well...
Not just mates, but to me...
...we're a lot more than that.
You know, every time I send you...
...one of those pictures that, um...
...maybe some direct messages too, that was just me and you.
There was a reason behind that.
And, well, today...
...I'd like you to know that.
So, um, I'm waiting for your answer, okay?
Cute! It's so innocent, too!
Thank you, Bachelor number three.
Good job.
All right, we have just one bachelor left. Bachelor number four, will you take the mic?
Steve.
Steve! Steve! Steve! Go!
Will, William, Matilda, and Steve.
Shiori is such a hitter.
Nerissa, my dearest...
I like you more than a friend.
Even... I don't know how you feel about me...
...and regardless of who you choose, whatever makes you happy...
...I will honor it, and I will hope that you will always...
...be happy with that person, whether it is...
...the beautiful Matilda...
...or the other people whose names I've forgotten.
You're just so wonderful, and your smile is precious.
Tips fedora.
Walks away with my $10 million of cash depending on how you answer.
Oh my gosh! So sweet!
That's so earnest, too! Wait, I wasn't expecting that from you, Bachelor #4, Steve!
No one ever expects that with a person with $10 million.
I know, right?
Well, how sweet! You guys all did so good! I feel my heart racing for sure!
And so, which one made your heart skip a beat the most, huh?
Well... the honest answer of who made my heart...
...stop... is Bachelor #2!
That's pretty good, yeah!
But I don't... it's... it's difficult to say.
I'll take that as a win! Yeah, it's pretty good.
It's difficult. Again, it's still hard to pick. I think we have to ask a few more questions before I can settle on one of you.
More? More?
Two more questions. So, shall we read off the next one?
Okay, let's go to the fourth question then! Okay. Okay.
The sweet days you'd longed for with Nerissa...
...It's been two years since you finally confessed your love. Two years!
And embraced something truly special between the two of you.
Everything seemed perfect...
...like a dream you never wanted to end. But...
...a tiny mistake on your part sparked a huge fight between the two of you.
With all your heart, apologize for the wrong you've done...
...and strive together to overcome this trial that threatens your love!
Okay.
So we've been dating for two years, and you guys have upset me.
So, won't you please apologize and make it all better?
I'll put my blindfold back on, so make things right between us, okay, you four?
Two years... Two years is pretty serious.
All right, Bachelor #1, it's your turn.
Okay, here I go!
Nerissa... I'm sorry.
I know I hurt you very deeply...
...with all my...
Well, it wasn't meant to be like this, but...
...ultimately, it turned out this way.
My... indecisiveness.
My... lack of action.
I know that you, the love of my life...
...I should have done it. I should have...
...already proposed to you, already have made you...
...long before, but...
I'm sorry for hurting you this way.
For hurting you at your core, in your heart so deeply.
Could you ever forgive me?
What a cutie!
Still, Bachelor #1, you managed to be so earnest and sweet!
You're really reaching to my heart. Let's move on to Bachelor #2...
...and see what sort of answer they're going to give.
Hey Nerissa. I know... I was gaming with the boys...
...and then you walked... you walked in, and you wanted attention...
...and I was like, "5 minutes, I can't pause the game! It's an online game, Nerissa!"
But... and then you went away crying...
...but after the gaming session, I was like, hmm, maybe I did do something wrong.
Maybe I should have invited her to play a game with me.
So, I'm going to do something that I've never done ever once in my life. I've never done this before.
Apologize.
I've never apologized to anyone ever, and I'm going to apologize to you now, so listen.
Sorry, I guess.
You want to be my player two?
I'll play with you instead of the boys.
Come here, baby girl.
That's, I think that's good, bachelor number two.
Let's move on to bachelor number three.
Did she love that? Oh my god.
Alright, bachelor number three to the mic, please.
Hey.
I know things have been a little weird recently, huh?
I wanted to say something.
Nerissa?
I'm sorry.
I know...
maybe I was acting a little childish.
I kept on saying things...
like, "You're stinky."
And...
you know, maybe you took that personally, but...
it's just, I was teasing you...
because I love you!
I love you, Nerissa Ravencroft!
I'm sorry.
And I just wanted to say...
is that, you're stinky.
But...
I love it. I love your stink.
That's enough!
Let's move to the last bachelor, bachelor number four.
That was really good.
What the hell?
What a beautiful stench.
So beautiful.
Okay. Last one!
Hey, Nerissa.
It's me, one of the boys.
I just wanted to say I'm sorry that...
the other person and I were gaming instead of hanging out with you.
Hello?
We were just having so much fun playing games together.
I should have been focused on you.
I'm crying right now!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry, as one of the boys.
This is your feet-in apology.
Thank you?
I guess in your universe, I have two boyfriends? I'm dating both you and bachelor number two.
I forgive you for that, too, by the way. Nerissa has to forgive you.
Oh, a very, very understanding lover.
It's understanding, we were gaming too hard, you know? It was so great.
Oh, that's good. Oh my god, you're...
Well, I think I'm getting closer to my answer of which one of these lovely bachelors I'm going to pick.
But I think we're going to maybe need one, one more question.
What? Oh, I won! Okay.
Wow! Let's move on to the final question!
And after this one...
Nerissa makes her decision of who she chooses, so...
Nerissa, please answer carefully, okay?
Choose from the heart, okay? From the heart.
From the heart.
Yeah, in fact, Nerissa, why don't you read the final question, so we can finally see.
Okay.
Question number five: "My Eternity".
This is your moment, bachelors.
Make the ultimate marriage proposal to me.
I've never made a marriage proposal before!
Marriage proposal!
Now's the time.
So, let me put my blindfold back on, and I'm looking forward to seeing your answers, or hearing them.
Two years, and she still can't see us.
Um... you know...
the marriage proposal... should we really be going to the mic?
Oh... um... oh.
I guess you guys can do whatever you'd like. Bachelor number one, will you approach?
Slow... thinking.
Slowly thinking.
Bachelor number one, do you not love me or something?
Where are you? It's such a special day, we've been out to dinner at my favorite restaurant.
Are you standing me up on such a special day?
Uh.
Um...
Nerissa Ravencroft...
Yes? What's so funny?
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Just like that! Just like that!
Please!
Yes!
She said yes! She said yes!
She said yes! Yes!
Congratulations!
I mean, we've been dating for two years, so it'd be mean.
We're getting married!
But that's bachelor number two.
Oh.
Wait, is that it?
Yeah.
Boom. I toss something on the ground, pick it up.
I know you're blindfolded, pick it up anyway... pick it up.
Pick it up!
What?
Pick...
Oh my god!
It was a ring! I put a ring on your finger! We're engaged!
It was like claws! That was so painful!
We're engaged now!
That's the wrong hand! That's the wrong hand!
I will marry you! Get out of here! Get out!
Get out!
That was so scary! I'm so scared!
Someone go comfort her now.
Please, no more harassment, bachelors.
Let's move on to bachelor... No more bachelor number two.
Bachelor number three, please.
Nerissa, baby, I'm back.
It's been many seasons that have passed...
...since we met.
Many memories.
Hard times, beautiful times.
Many tears we shed together as we watched the sunrise.
I'd like to spend many more sunrises and sunsets together.
Will you be my everything?
Yes!
Oh, that was so sweet!
Bachelor number three, you're so sweet!
I don't feel like I should clap.
All right. You don't have to. It's okay.
One more contestant, bachelor number four, would you please...
What? What? What? What?
Approach?
What?
My bro.
Yes?
You are, like, the bro-est of my life.
Wait, what the heck's going on?
Thanks.
We've been gaming for, like, two years or more.
Yeah, bro, we have.
I know! I love playing farming games with you.
Hello?
I love playing shooting games with you. You are...
...my number two. Or my number one even. I'll be your number two.
Hello?
Wow.
You're just... I just love you so much, my bro.
Oh, thanks, bro.
Yeah. Will you marry me?
What? Yes! Yes!
Well, I think I'll disqualify...
...bachelor number four.
Get out of here!
They got married! They got married!
And with that, the questions are through.
Oh!
We've had some awesome love... awesome, maybe if you can call it that, love stories born.
Some good, some bad.
From one to four, whose story did you like the most?
Please reveal the partner, Nerissa! Yes! Who is the most romantic?
I'm going to go backwards, actually.
Drumroll, drumroll!
I think it's... it's obvious which bachelor did not steal my heart today.
Oh, that way, huh?
Okay, drumroll, drumroll!
Bachelor number two, step forward.
You are disqualified!
No!
All right. Bachelor number four, step forward.
You are disqualified!
Somehow, I feel like I knew it was you two.
I don't know what you're talking about. Come on, wifey.
This is the hard part now.
I'm between bachelor number one and bachelor number three.
Who stole my heart the most?
Was it the earnest bachelor number one?
Or the very sweet bachelor number three who seemed to know me best?
I can't decide!
But if I had to pick between this impossible decision...
...I'd have to pick... bachelor number three!
Wait!
It's okay! You can choose her! It's okay! You can play with her!
Yeah, we're married! We're married!
But, I must say, knowing that each of you thought so deeply about a life with me...
...except some of you maybe...
...it makes me feel so special on my special day.
So thank you for warming my heart.
Aw, happy birthday!
Congrats! Yay!
Yay!
Oh, matching! Awesome!
Happy birthday, I guess.
Happy birthday!
Oh, Rissa.
You're so fluffy.
Oh... I love you. I love you, too.
Oh, baw baw!
Baw baw! Baw baw forever!
Baw baw!
What a wonderful birthday this is.
I've even found a wonderful partner.
It feels like this next year of my life is going to be so amazing.
Rissa, wait, baby!
Hey, the flirting is over!
Snap back to reality. Oh, let's play Twister!
Oh, yeah!
I got Twister ready so we can all play together!
Looking at it, it might be a bit tricky for all five of us to play at once, though.
Yeah, I think you might be right. What should we do then?
Umm, well, how about to make it fun, we can play one at a time?
You know what, actually, I just thought of a special rule for today.
Let's call the game... Posing Twister!
Posing Twister!
As the name suggests, the rule is to strike poses while playing Twister.
For example, if the instruction says:
Right hand on red, and cat pose.
You place your right hand on red and do the cat pose.
Once all four limbs are in position, you can move just one limb to strike the specific pose.
The time limit will be one minute, and if you can keep your balance for the full minute...
you can clear the challenge.
But if you lose your balance at any point, the game is over.
Quick question!
Oh, yes?
Can the audience mess with the player?
Why not? Sure!
So, who wants to go first?
What? Oh, we were just explaining, so somebody else go first!
I guess I'll face the king! Alright, I'll go! Okay!
Okay, do your best, Mococo-chan!
I'll show you how it's done, okay?!
I'll try my best to distract you, so do your best!
I've never played Twister before. This is my first time doing it.
Well, you've got one minute, okay? Do your best.
Are we ready?
Then let's start! Go!
Okay, first up: left foot on green, and wolf pose!
Awoo!
Okay, next: right hand on red, and cat pose!
Make some fast poses! Right hand! Faster, faster!
Right hand... Syaaa!
Left foot on blue, cow pose!
Cow? Cow? Moo! Moo!
Moo!
All right, right hand on red, and hero pose!
Right hand on red and hero! Hero! Hero!
Wait, but my right hand is already on red! Oh!
Oh, right hand on red again. I can't help it.
Left hand on yellow, and happy pose!
Happy, happy! So happy! Happy, happy, happy!
Now place your left foot on yellow and express anger!
I'm furious!
So much rage! Rage! Angry pose!
You did so good!
Congrats!
It feels like I am split apart! Ah! Ah!
You did so good! All right, Mococo! You passed with flying colors!
Whoa!
Oh, fall! Are you okay? Nice try, Mococo!
All right, who's next, Mococo?
Umm, well... We get to choose! Ah... Bijou!
Why me?! You're next because you made fun of me at the beginning!
Yeah, okay, I'll do it, then!
And because of that, I'm going to be your biggest distraction, okay?!
How about I tell Bijou what to do then?
Okay. All right, let's start!
Right foot on blue. Okay.
Now give me a graceful queen pose.
Oh! Ho ho ho! Oh, my! Miss Elizabeth is on it!
Left foot on blue!
Now do a lion pose!
Grrr!
Left hand on red!
Give me a rabbit pose!
Rabbit? What does a rabbit say?
Figure it out, I'm not a rabbit!
Peko! Peko!
Now place your right foot on green...
...and go BAU BAU!
BAU BAU! BAU BAU!
Left foot on red!
Now give us your best "grr" pose!
Grrr!
Right hand on blue!
Now kawaii! Go kawaii!
Kawaii! Kawaii desu! Kawaii kara yurushite!
I'm cute! I'm cute, so please forgive me!
Good enough for me.
Did I win?
You didn't lose your balance,
but I didn't think that was a very cute pose at the end. What about you, Fuwawa?
No, it wasn't cute enough.
But you did your best. Good job, Biboo!
Alright, you pick who's next, Biboo.
Okay, Shiori! You go next! Okay, Shiori, let's do this!
Alright, boss babe round!
Okay, Shiori, are you ready?
I guess so!
Let's start!
Left foot...
...on yellow!
Yellow, got it!
And now, you're going to show us... baby Shiori!
Waah! Waah!
Okay, now...
...again, left foot on yellow!
And horse pose!
Neigh! Neigh!
Okay, next is right hand on blue!
Got it!
And now... give us your coolest prince pose!
Will you marry me?
Okay, let's stop this. Right foot on yellow!
Okay.
And witch pose!
This is my broom somewhere here.
Okay, now your left hand on red!
Okay.
And do a bear pose!
I am already in bear pose. Grrr!
Okay, you're going to take your right hand, put it onto yellow...
...and you're going to do a butterfly pose!
I am wiggling like a butterfly! I'm flying!
No, you're not!
You did so good, Shiori!
You're actually so good at this!
I think Fuwawa's up!
Okay! I don't know if I'm going to be good, but I can try my best!
Okay, Fuwawa, go on! Do your best now!
Okay, let's start!
Okay, right foot on green and do a hula dance move!
Right foot on green?
Right!
Okay.
Hula!
Left foot on yellow for dolphin pose!
Oh no, they need water! Safe!
Okay, next! Right hand on red, fighting pose!
Right hand on red?
Good luck with that!
I can't... oh no!
You can do it! Fight, fight!
Okay, okay! Next!
Right foot on yellow, puppy pose!
That's her default!
You can't take your hands off!
Okay, right foot... right foot...
BAU BAU!
Well, that's what I have to do!
Alright, Nerissa, it's your turn now!
Okay, I'm ready to blow you all out of the water!
Oh, you think you can? No, I don't actually. Alright, show us your flexibility! Are you ready?
I'm ready!
Let's start! Alright, first up, left foot on green with a sexy pose!
Sexy pose!
Wow! Oh!
All right!
Right foot on yellow, but even sexier!
Oh! Oh my gosh! Wow!
All right,
left hand on blue, wet cat Rissa pose!
Meow! Meow! Rissa!
Oh my god! What is that?
All right,
right foot on green, sea lion pose!
Right foot on... sea lion?!
Sea lion pose? Swim, swim, swim!
Arf, arf, arf! You don't know how to sea lion?
Anyway, anyway!
Right hand on blue and do one push-up.
Oh, one push... push-up! Oh, this way?
That's real! Nice!
All right, left hand on red, octopus pose!
Oh! Wiggle, wiggle...
Wiggle wiggle! Nice! You look like an octopus!
All right, left foot on blue, pirate pose!
Arr! Nice!
What?!
Yay! We did it! You did so good!
Thank you!
How do you like my posing, everyone?
Beautiful! Yeah!
I liked the slide!
Wow, those were good sexy poses. Yeah!
Can we all do a sexy pose together? Okay, okay!
Which leg? This... this one!
Okay, sexy pose everyone! One, two...
Wait, what is sexy? Well, yeah!
Don't stop yet! Again!
One, two, three...
Wow! Amela, wow!
Okay, now... Is my foot showing?
Oh, yeah! One more? Left? Okay, okay.
Okay, here we go. One, two, three...
Ugh! Very nice, ladies!
Ow! My wrist... I'm confused.
That's enough though.
Yeah, I think we're done with Twister.
Okay, no more fun.
Well, what should we do next then?
Well... actually...
I was thinking, maybe we could do...
karaoke together?
Oh! Karaoke! Yeah, I want to sing!
All right, let's do it! Let's go!
Karaoke! Yeah!
And now, please enjoy...
Dark Breath!
da da la la da la dark
ra pa pan pan pan
you will want it more , want it more
You will want it more, want it more
ra pa pan pan pan
ey ！ you will love it now , love it
Ey! You will love it now, love it
ra pa pan pan
風穴開けたんだ
I've blasted a hole open
支配は始まった
The dominion has begun
息はもう掛けたの
I've already cast my breath over you
but you don't know
自覚ないはずよ
You shouldn't even be aware of it
( huff - n - puff )
huff-n-puff
抑え切れない自力制御不能な power
An uncontrollable power I cannot suppress on my own
捕まえてみなよ 影も形もない my heart
Try to catch my heart, which has neither shadow nor form
間違えてた道に導くの全て遊び
Being guided down the wrong path, it's all just a game.
そう、終わり
Yes, the end.
誰もが羨む桃源郷へとチェンジ
Changing into a paradise that everyone envies.
天体の情熱 衝動を頂戴
Give me celestial passion and impulses...
満載に満たしてね
...and fill me up to the brim.
誰にも気づかれないけど
Though no one will notice...
手に入れるわ、これで
...I'll make it mine with this.
Rat-tat-tat-tat-tat
Got to be kidding me, 癖になるでしょう？
You've got to be kidding me, you'll get addicted, right?
Rat-tat-tat-tat-tat
脳を急激に射抜かれてるのよ
My brain is being shot through so rapidly.
Oh no
そう、退屈で退屈でしょ？
Yes, you're bored, so bored, right?
普通じゃない衝動
A highly unusual impulse.
一歩踏み出せばいいかも
Maybe just taking one step forward is fine.
済ませて、Rat-tat-tat-tat-tat
Get it over with, rat-tat-tat-tat-tat!
Wow! Wow!
Nerissa!
Are you ready?
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん？
[On-Screen Title: How About Paipai Kamen?]
苦い恋の果て残された
Left behind at the end of a bitter love...
出どころ不明の金の山
...is a mountain of gold of unknown origin.
あいつの気配がするものばかりは
All the things carrying his trace...
未練ばかりで食えやしない
...are full of regret and completely useless.
あたしは生きながら化けてでる
I transform while still alive...
鏡の前で早変わり
...making a quick change in front of the mirror.
パイパイ仮面でどうかしらん？
How about Paipai Kamen?
今宵もひと暴れ
I'll go wild tonight too!
踊れ踊り踊れみだれ髪
Dance, dance, dance! Disheveled hair...
はずむ胸
...and bouncing breasts!
匿名のワナに酔いしれて
Getting drunk on an anonymous trap...
Shine a spot...
Shine a spotlight on me now!
パイ パイパイ パイパイパイ ヤッパイ
Pai, paipai, paipaipai, yappai!
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
Paipai Kamen is a multi-millionaire!
パイ パイパイ パイパイパイ ヤッパイ
Pai, paipai, paipaipai, yappai!
黄金の蝶 舞いあがれ
Golden butterflies, soar high!
ほらほら踊れよ
Look, look, dance!
散財万歳コインシャワー
Hurray for spending! Coin shower!
刹那を生きろよ
Live in the moment!
瞬間クライマックス
Climax of the moment!
浮世忘れてふけるダンシングハイ
Forget this fleeting world, indulge in a dancing high!
パイヤパイヤ
Paiya, paiya!
discothèque queen アア パイパイ仮面
Discothèque queen, ah, Paipai Kamen!
Pai! Pai! Pai!...
Fuwawa!
Hi!
Singing this song together...
...what do we both have in common?
Uh... um...
Come on, you say it!
Okay...
O-PAIPAI!
Wow wow!
悪い奴だとは知りつつも
Even though I know he is a bad guy...
恋は盲目とめどなく
...love is blind and endless.
愛のために血も青くした保存
I even turned my blood blue for love.
あたしはとんまな道化師さ
I'm just a foolish clown.
|虫籠の蝶は飛ばなけりゃ
If a butterfly in a cage doesn't fly...
虫ケラのままで終わっちまう
...it ends up as just an ordinary bug.
パイパイ仮面が解き放つ
Paipai Kamen unleashes them.
今宵も羽ばたけよ
Spread your wings tonight as well!
喰らえ喰らい喰らえケダモノよ
Take this, take this, beasts!
クセモノよ
You rascals!
求めよさらば与えられん
Ask, and it shall be given to you!
Shine a spot...
Shine a spotlight on me now!
パイ パイパイ パイパイパイ ヤッパイ
Pai, paipai, paipaipai, yappai!
パイパイ仮面はボンキュッボン
Paipai Kamen is perfectly curvaceous!
パイ パイパイ パイパイパイ ヤッパイ
Pai, paipai, paipaipai, yappai!
視線の先はスキャンダル
Every gaze leads to a scandal.
どんどん揺らせよ
Keep shaking it!
フラッシュアワーにバイブレーション
Vibration in the flash hour!
サイケに染まれよ
Get dyed in psychedelic colors!
泡沫バブルモーション
Transient bubble motion!
一瞬でゾーンにはいるダンシングハイ
Entering the zone in an instant...
ダンシングハイ パイヤパイヤ
...dancing high, paiya paiya!
discothèque queen アア パイパイ仮面
Discothèque queen, ah, Paipai Kamen!
今日もあいつはどこかの国でどんな悪さしてるやら
I wonder what mischief he is up to in some country today.
あたしはいつでもあんたの港
I will always be your harbor.
疲れた時には戻っておいで
Come back to me when you're tired.
Come back to me when you are tired.
バイ バイバイ バイバイバイバイ
Bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
バイバイ仮面で行こう
Let's go with the bye-bye mask!
バイ バイバイ バイバイバイバイ
Bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar high!
ホ、ホ、ホ、踊れよ
Ho, ho, ho, dance!
万歳 万歳 コインシャワー
Hooray, hooray, coin shower!
手をつなぎ生きろよ
Hold hands and live on!
瞬間 瞬間 クライマックス
Climax after climax!
浮き世を忘れてふける ダンスインハイ
Forget the fleeting world and indulge in Dancing High!
ディスコティッククイーン
Discotheque Queen!
あー バイバイ仮面
Ah, bye-bye mask!
ディスコティッククイーン
Discotheque Queen!
あー バイバイ仮面
Ah, bye-bye mask!
まわる まわる まわる まわルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning, mawa Ruuna!
まわる まわる まわる まわルーナ ルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning, mawa Ruuna, Ruuna!
まわる まわる まわる まわルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning, mawa Ruuna!
まわる まわる 地球を ぐるぐる
Spinning, spinning, spinning around the Earth!
またたく間に街中が
In the blink of an eye, the whole town...
まわる まわる あたま くらくら
...spins and spins, making our heads dizzy!
幕が上がり 祭りの始まり
The curtain rises, the festival begins!
回れ 舞われ 眉を開いたら
Spin and dance, once your eyebrows part!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
みんな ぐるぐるぐるる 回って
Everyone spin round and round!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
ずっと ぐるぐるぐるる まわルーナ
Spinning forever, mawa Ruuna!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Round and round, laugh together!
もっと ぐるぐる 笑って
Laugh together even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 踊って
Round and round, dance together!
みんな ぐるぐるぐるる 踊って
Everyone dance round and round!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる そうやって
Round and round, just like that!
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Round and round, laugh together!
ずっと ぐるぐるぐるる まわルーナ
Spinning forever, mawa Ruuna!
回り過ぎたら
If we spin too much...
世界の暗闇が
...the world's darkness...
みんなを包む
...will envelop everyone.
恐怖乱舞も守るから
I'll protect you even from the wild dance of fear!
ぐるぐる
Guruguru...
地球は
The Earth...
回り
...began...
始め
...to spin...
幾
...billions...
億
...of...
年
...years ago.
いつまでも
Forever and ever,
このまま
just like this...
回る
...it spins,
みんなに
bringing...
幸せを
...happiness to everyone.
まわりつづく まわルーナ
It keeps spinning, mawa Ruuna!
ますますます 社会が ぐるぐる
The society is spinning more and more.
まーあれ？
Huh, is it spinning?
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
みんな ぐるぐるぐるる 回って
Everyone spin round and round!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
ずっと ぐるぐるぐるる まわルーナ
Spinning forever, mawa Ruuna!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Round and round, laugh together!
もっと ぐるぐる 笑って
Laugh together even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 踊って
Round and round, dance together!
みんな ぐるぐるぐるる 踊って
Everyone dance round and round!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる そうやって
Round and round, just like that!
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 笑って
Round and round, laugh together!
ずっと ぐるぐるぐるる まわルーナ
Spinning forever, mawa Ruuna!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
みんな ぐるぐるぐるる 回って
Everyone spin round and round!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
もっと ぐるぐる 回って
Spin around even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って
Round and round, spin around!
ずっと ぐるぐるぐるる まわルーナ んなー
Spinning forever, mawa Ruuna, nnaa~
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って もっと
Spinning round and round, even more!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる 回って んなー
Spinning round and round, nnaa~
ぐるぐる まわる まわる まわルーナ！
Spinning, spinning, spinning, mawa Ruuna!
Let's go, advent!
ぽ、ぽ、ぽ、ぽ...
Po, po, po, po...
ぽっ、ぽっ
Poppop!
ぽい！ぽい！
Poi! Poi!
ポポポポポポポポポポポ
Popopopopopopopopopopo
ポポポポポポポポポポ
Popopopopopopopopo
ポポポポポポポポポ
Popopopopopopopo
ポポポポポポポポポポ
Popopopopopopopopo
ポポポポポ
Popopopo
ポポポポポポポポ
Popopopopopopo
あははは！
Ahahaha!
Mayday, mayday.
mayday 声は届いてる？
Mayday, can you hear my voice?
心がズキッと痛いみたい
It feels like my heart is throbbing with pain.
baby なんて魅力的
Baby, you're so attractive.
見せるテクニックはすぐにクラクラ
The techniques you show make me dizzy instantly.
mayday それじゃ物足りない
Mayday, that's not enough.
すぐにもっともっと欲しがるスタイル
This style makes me want more and more right away.
hey hey もっと焦らしてよ
Hey, hey, tease me some more.
あなたの心に入ってたいの
I want to get inside your heart.
Ah 見透かした甘い罠
Ah, a sweet trap I saw right through.
Ah ハマってあげようか
Ah, should I fall into it for you?
Ah 自在にコントロールして
Ah, control me however you want.
一途なはずなのに
I'm supposed to be single-minded, yet...
フラフラって酔っちゃいそうな甘い匂い誘われ
Tempted by a sweet scent that makes me dizzy...
フラフラって寄っちゃうわ あぁもう help me...
Wandering closer and closer, oh my, help me...
逃げたいわけじゃないから これくらいがちょうどいいわ
It's not that I want to run away, so this much is just right.
なんでもうキミの前じゃ絶対 help me して
Why is it that in front of you, I always say 'help me'?
mayday 舵が取れないの
Mayday, I can't steer.
気持ちがモヤッと晴れないし
This hazy feeling just won't clear up.
baby なんかじゃいられない
I can't just be a 'baby'.
まだひるむのがワンワンワン
I'm still hesitant, bow-wow-wow.
絶対にありえないじゃない
There's absolutely no way, right?
これはただの勘違い
This is just a misunderstanding.
衝動的なのはNO、NOだ
Being impulsive is a big no-no.
大人びているこの価値観
These values are so mature.
だってね溶け出すような体温に魅せられて
But you see, I'm enchanted by a body heat that feels like melting.
なんか変 あたしじゃないみたい
Something is strange, it doesn't feel like me.
あぁもう rescue me...
Oh my, rescue me...
嫌々って漏れちゃうくらいにあたしを困らせて
Trouble me so much that my protests slip out.
なんかもつれてて なんかもうあたしからは絶対 rescue me して
Somehow entangled, so please rescue me, because I definitely can't say it.
ねえ どうして
Hey, why...
愛はいたずらするんだろう
...does love play tricks on us?
ねえ いつかは
Hey, will this pain...
この痛みも消えるの
...ever disappear someday?
本来は案外簡単に否定して壊れちゃうけど
Normally, it would be easily denied and broken, but...
傷だらけの心は...
...this heart covered in wounds is...
気が付けば手を伸ばしてその遠さ苦しくて
Before I know it, I stretch out my hand, and the distance is painful.
キミも手を伸ばしてくれたら
If you would only reach out your hand too...
いいの？ 吸っちゃっていいの？
Is it okay? Is it okay to suck your blood?
「もう無理もう無理」なんて 悪い子だね
Saying "No more, no more," what a bad child.
いたい いたい
It hurts, it hurts...
ここにいて
...stay here with me.
やっと見つけた落ち着く場所
I finally found a place to settle down,
その手で触れていてよ
so keep touching me with those hands.
ほら メーデー
Look, mayday!
グラグラで酔っちゃいそうなの
I feel so dizzy, like I'm getting drunk.
曖昧 触らないで
Vaguely, don't touch me.
ユラユラで酔っちゃうわ
Wobbling, I'm getting drunk.
もう最低
This is already the worst.
Help me, help me
Rescue me, rescue me
Save me, save me
メーデー
Mayday!
どうしても突き通したい
I want to push through no matter what.
どうにも守りきれぬ
I can't protect it no matter what.
凍って溢れ出したんだ
Frozen, it started to overflow.
もう SOS
No more, SOS.
した
I did.
Huzzah!
Woo!
Hey! Birthday, birthday!
Happy Birthday, Nerissa!
Thank you!
And you... you better have a freaking wonderful rest of your day because I'm... I'm monitoring you, alright?
You... you got it, Liz.
Thanks for the invite.
For justice!
Oh! Uh...
and she's gone.
Goodbye, Liz! I love you!
Good day, Nerissa Ravencroft,
mother of my child!
Happy Birthday!
(put your hands up, put your, put your hands up)
いかにも 蛸にも お腹 goo goo
Indeed, even for octopuses, our stomachs are rumbling
手にもつ 少なめ いざ zun zun
Holding just a bit in hand, off we go, rumbling forward
飯は食わねば 寝る寝る never ナ
Must eat rice, or else we'll sleep, sleep, never!
タイムスリップ いー ya ここどこ 迷子で go go go
Time slip? Oh well, where is this? Lost and go, go, go!
dancing ダーウィン じゃんじゃん 進化 進行
Dancing Darwin, rapidly evolving and progressing!
干渉あり 人類発祥どうこう
With interference, something about the origin of humanity
ァ 良い感じ そろそろ 出発 進行
Ah, feeling good, it's about time to depart!
去るもの 追わ猿 ぱぱぴぱぷ～
Those who leave, we monkeys won't chase, pa-pa-pi-pa-pu~
(put your hands up, put your, put your hands up)
欲しいモンは ほら これだろ 旦那
Look, this is what you want, master!
さぁ わんわん わんわん わんっ ワンッ
Now, woof-woof, woof-woof, bow-wow!
チキチキ ワッハー！
Chiki chiki wah-hah!
脳内全開 yeah やっぱっぱっ party
Brain at full throttle, yeah, definitely a party!
笑って泣いて踊れば あいあいあっおー
If we laugh, cry, and dance, aye-aye-oh!
パンドラ開いて ドヴァって飲まれた raw
Open Pandora's box and get swallowed raw!
ごらん遊ばせ
Take a look!
あちゃちゃいちゃいちゃいちゃいちゃっパリーン
A-cha-cha, flirting and flirting, crash!
おーわっあっ アイアイ
Oh-wah-ah, eye-eye!
気分は high とんとん たん
Feeling high, ton-ton-tan!
おーわっあっ アイアイ
Oh-wah-ah, eye-eye!
愛の間合い どんどん ぱん
The distance of love, don-don-pan!
つながってんだ 記録なんだ gene & meme だ
Connected by records of gene and meme!
連綿つむいだ 犬猿人神
Continuously spun: dog, monkey, human, god!
報酬いいんだ 働いてんだ 連勤なんだ
Rewards are good, working consecutive days!
休みなし 毎日が月月金土あーん
No days off, every day is Mon-Mon-Fri-Sat, ahn~
乱心ダーウィン じゃんじゃん 淘汰 進行
Wild Darwin, rapidly weeding out and progressing!
人類抹消 あるでしょ ai 暴走
Human extinction is likely with AI running amok!
ァ もう最深部 そろそろ 計画 進行
Ah, reaching the deepest part, about time to proceed with the plan!
もうゆびゆびまでわんつっすりー
Ready up to your fingers, one-two-three!
おらよーおらよーだんだんすやぁ…
Here we go, here we go, gradually falling asleep...
I'm dying!
Thank you forever!
オーマイガ オーマイ ワイフ ようやく真理辿り着いた
Oh my god, oh my wife, finally reached the truth!
無限螺旋抜け 無心で
Escaped the infinite spiral, empty-minded!
ほらウェーイ ほらウェーイ
Look, yay, look, yay!
Happy Birthday, Nerissa!
(put your hands up, put your, put your hands up)
去るもの 追わ猿 ぱぱぴぱぷ～
Those who leave, we monkeys won't chase, pa-pa-pi-pa-pu~
さぁ わんわん わんわん わんっ ワンッ
Now, woof-woof, woof-woof, bow-wow!
チキチキ ワッハー！
Chiki chiki wah-hah!
脳内全開 yeah やっぱっぱっ party
Brain at full throttle, yeah, definitely a party!
笑って泣いて踊れば あいあいあっおー
If we laugh, cry, and dance, aye-aye-oh!
パンドラ開いて ドヴァって飲まれた raw
Open Pandora's box and get swallowed raw!
ごらん遊ばせ
Take a look!
あちゃちゃいちゃいちゃいちゃいちゃっパリーン
A-cha-cha, flirting and flirting, crash!
おーわっあっ アイアイ
Oh-wah-ah, eye-eye!
気分は high とんとん たん
Feeling high, ton-ton-tan!
おーわっあっ アイアイ
Oh-wah-ah, eye-eye!
愛の間合い どんどん ぱん
The distance of love, don-don-pan!
(put your hands up, put your, put your hands up)
Put your hands up
Nerissa, Happy Birthday!
And now to wrap things...
Let's go ahead and introduce this year's birthday merch!
Yay!
Please take a look at the set. There's also going to be a limited set that comes with an autographed postcard!
Wow!
So let's take a look at all the details!
First up, can you believe it? I made a Jailbird onesie!
Isn't it so cute?
Oh, it looks so nice.
It looks so comfy!
It's perfect if you want to let out your inner Fat Flock member. You can wear it to sleep...
...you can wear it out. Who cares? You wear it wherever you want. It's a kigurumi!
So, do consider picking it up. Please.
All right! And then next item is...
...the Jailbird Beanie!
Do you want to look cool?
Do you want to look nonchalant while also repping the Jailbirds?
Repping the Fat Flock?
Then you can with this piping beanie. It even has...
...a Jailbird embroidery on it. Look at the little horns!
It's so cool and cute at the same time.
And now, with the third item!
Ya-hoo! This is so cool!
Cool as ice, I might say.
The Jailbird ice tray!
It can make six different Jailbird ice cubes!
They're so cute! Look at all those expressions too!
I can't wait to use this and put this in my matcha lattes!
What do you think? What are you going to use it for, Rissa?
Uh, I don't know. I think I'm gonna put it in matcha lattes too, but I think I could just put it in anything.
You could just take them, you could chuck them too.
Not at people, but like, at the floor.
Although people would be okay too. No, no, no, no, no, no!
Okay, let's see what's next! This one!
And with this, the "Day-Out With Nerissa" acrylic keychain!
You can take it along with you. Take Nerissa everywhere you go and take photos!
You know, just like, uh, you're uploading it...
...to, to my favorite app, Nerissa Ravencroft. That's the best one.
What? My favorite app?
It says, "Day-Out Nerissa Ravencroft".
Yes! This illustration is done by my mama as well!
So, it'd be awesome if you would share photos with this item on SNS...
...using the hashtag #DateWithNerissa.
Please. Did you just... never mind.
And of course, there's also a birthday set that includes a postcard and a bonus voice pack.
Along with these four items.
Only the limited edition comes with an autographed postcard.
So don't wait, get yours now for your Fat Flock friends!
Now, what's this "Day-Out With Nerissa" bonus voice pack like, huh?
Do you have a preview?
I guess I could tell you a little bit about it.
It's actually based off of the illustration.
So, uh, it's a day out, similar to the dates that you guys came up with.
I'm going to be going on a date with the Jailbirds to the amusement park.
So you can look forward to the shenanigans that ensue.
Shenanigans! Always shenanigans. It's such a grass.
Anyways, I worked really hard to come up with all this merch so that everybody could enjoy it.
So be sure to grab yours as soon as it goes live! The link will be in the description.
Well, this turned out to be such a wonderful birthday!
And Advent, I'm so happy that we could celebrate all together as well.
It made it so special for me!
Happy Birthday, Nerissa!
Yeah, and we also had Justice's guests too, singing with me.
So thank you Justice for coming and celebrating with me as well!
And most of all, thank you Jailbirds!
Thank you everyone! Have a great day!
Bye-bye!
Jailbirds, thank you for coming to my 3rd Birthday here in hololive! You've truly made the last few years of my life so incredibly memorable.
I can't wait to see where this next year of my life with Advent, hololive, and you takes me!
Thanks for always supporting me, and let's keep doing our best!!! -Nerissa